<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Soby Chacko</title>
    <link>https://sobychacko.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Soby Chacko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sobychacko&#34;&gt;Soby Chacko&lt;/a&gt; 2019</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sobychacko.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic stateful streaming application using Spring Cloud Stream and Kafka Streams</title>
      <link>https://sobychacko.github.io/posts/kafka-streams-binder-stateful-basic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sobychacko.github.io/posts/kafka-streams-binder-stateful-basic/</guid>
      <description>Continuing on what we started here, in this blog, we are looking at how a basic stateful stream application can be written using Spring Cloud Stream and Kafka Streams.
Writing a stateless streaming application is very straightforward in Spring Cloud Stream, but when you have to include state about your data, then we have more things to worry about. Kafka Streams make it really easy to write stateful applications and Spring Cloud Stream provides tighter integrations for that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Cloud Stream and Kafka Streams - Basics</title>
      <link>https://sobychacko.github.io/posts/kafka-streams-binder-basic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sobychacko.github.io/posts/kafka-streams-binder-basic/</guid>
      <description>In this blog, we are going to explore how Spring Cloud Stream and Kafka Streams can be used to write basic stateless stream processing applications. Kafka Streams is a great library for writing very powerful streaming applications and Spring Cloud Stream provides a very familiar programming model to making the task of writing such applications easier. The application that we develop is a very trivial one, but it will introduce the basic programming model that can be used for advanced applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>